sciencespot.net 2016-12-01

# The Science Spot

(Last update: July 2015)

### What information do you gather? How is it used? Who has access to it?

This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. 

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifiable information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via the "Contact Me" form on our website.

_Note:   Users who may submit questions or comments through the site's Contact Me form will have the option to provide additional information for the webmaster to use to contact them with a response or answers.  E-mail addresses will not be shared with any other parties and are only visible to the webmaster._

### What security measures do you have in place to protect my personal information? How does your site use cookies?

To safeguard your personal information, we do not share information with any third party with the exception for advertisers as outlined below.

Third party advertisers on our site, such as Sovrn, Hot Chalk Network/Mode, and Google AdSense, may use cookies for tracking purposes. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet. Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

For more information about opting out of Google AdSense cookies, please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**  
We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [ http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [ http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).
